Some girls are out of this world
How to Talk to Girls at Parties is a comedy, music,
romance film directed by John Cameron Mitchell.
In 1970s London, a teenage outsider named Enn falls in love with a
rebellious alien girl named Zan, who has come to Earth for a party.
Together, they navigate the complexities of
intergalactic culture and the trials of first love.
Zan, played by Elle Fanning.
Enn, played by Alex Sharp.
Boadicea, played by Nicole Kidman.
PT Wain, played by Matt Lucas.
PT Stella, played by Ruth Wilson.
Vic, played by Abraham Lewis.
How to Talk to Girls at Parties is a 2017 science fiction romantic comedy film directed by John Cameron Mitchell from a
screenplay he co-wrote with Philippa Goslett, based on the 2006 short story of the same name by Neil Gaiman.
The film stars Elle Fanning, Alex Sharp, Ruth
Wilson, Matt Lucas and Nicole Kidman.
Principal photography began on 9 November 2015 in Sheffield.
The film had its world premiere at the Cannes Film Festival on 21 May 2017.
It was released in the United Kingdom on 11 May 2018 by StudioCanal
UK and in the United States on 25 May 2018 by A24.
The film explores themes of galaxy, london, england, 1970s, punk rock, alien.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.